Look! Another shooting star!
Did you remember to make a
wish this time, buddy?
Oh... I forgot...
[cat meows]
Are you serious?
What do you mean you're going out?
The guys are getting together.
I'm allowed to go out sometimes,
you know.
Sometimes?
It's been every night lately.
I'll come home early, alright?
Thanks for coming!
Sure, I'll be back.
I know.
Come on, let's go home.
[Kakashi sighs]
Look, why don't we just do rock,
paper, scissors again?
Oh, come on!
There must be something more exciting we
can do!
And you call yourself my rival?
We have to get an early start tomorrow,
so let's just take a pass on tonight.
A mission is no excuse!
I have all this pent-up
energy inside me, so there's no
better time than right now
for some really rigorous training!
Honest to goodness,
discipline and hard work
will lead us to success
in future missions!
Are you even listening to me?!
Forget that for now.
Do you sense something strange?
As if there was suddenly a dark chill in
the air?
The only thing that's chilly is your
attitude!
You must be much more hot-blooded!
It's a full moon tonight, Sasuke.
[infant starts]
[chuckles]
[wind howling]
[gasps]
What is this?
I'm feeling... something ominous.
[infant whines]
[sighs]
There, there, it's okay.
Don't cry, Sasuke.
No matter what happens, your big brother
will protect you, I promise you that.
Hm?
Hmm
[exhales smoke]
It can't be.
[explosion]
[screaming]
[coughing]
Is that..?
[growling]
[gasp]
No, no way!
[roars]
The Ninetales!
[screaming]
[growling]
[roars]
[screaming]
[infant crying]
Hey. It's okay.
[grunts]
It's the Ninetales!
The demon fox is loose!
What?
What's going on?!
Just run, you idiot!
[screaming]
Aah!
[cries]
Sasuke... It's okay now.
I know that was a little scary.
[crying continues]
Lord Third, it's the Ninetales!
The Ninetales is inside the village!
Yes, I know that.
I'll go restrain him.
You and the others go protect all the
people of the village.
Yes, sir!
Was Kushina's seal broken?
We failed even with all the safeguards we
put in place.
Biwako.
Damn you, Ninetales!
It's time to release all my pent-up
energy!
We don't know what we're up against.
Come on!
I'll be your opponent!
Wait!
Huh?
Gather immediately in the guard room.
Why?
The third Hokage ordered it!
What?
Lord Hiruzen did?
Well, you heard him.
Let's go, Guy.
[yells]
Huurrrrgh!
Now is our chance!
All of you, go!
Evacuate the village!
Are we ready?
Yeah.
Over here, Ninetales!
Hyah!
Right here!
Your battle's here!
With me!
[grunts]
[Ninetails roars]
Do not falter!
Even if we can't defeat the Ninetales,
we must allow the villagers to escape!
[gasp]
Don't take action on your own!
Assemble around Lord Hiruzen!
Carry out your orders!
As Hokage, I must protect the village.
My family.
This is what I have to do right now.
[growls]
[growling]
[roars]
[screaming]
Iruka, are you all right?
Mom, what's the matter?
Dad, look, it's Mom!
She's been hit!
Why didn't you stay at the shelter,
Iruka?
Leave your mother to me.
You hurry up and get out of here,
now!
No, Dad!
I'm not just gonna run away and leave you
and Mom behind here!
I'm gonna stay and protect Mom!
Don't you dare push me, son!
It's a parent's duty to protect their
children!
We have to protect the village!
We need to drive the Ninetales outside the
village walls!
Right!
Buy me some time so I can ready my jutsu!
Do not let up the attack!
Yes, sir!
Let's go!
[woosh]
[roaring]
[screaming]
Ninja Art Summoning!
Monkey King Enma, appear!
The Ninetales, huh?
So the seal was broken.
We'll drive it from the village.
With the Adamantine Nyoi!
Transformation, gotcha!
Now, Enma! Let's go!
Right!
Extend!
[roars]
Good, it's been driven out of the village!
Now keep at him!
One after another!
Hold the attack, all of you!
Wait for the fourth hokage!
[groaning]
Iruka...
No, let me go!
My mom and dad are still fighting back
there!
The barriers disappeared!
Lord Fourth!
Lady Kushina.
Take her to the hospital right away.
Summon the medical ninja.
Please, Lord Third.
Kushina...
I beg you, please take care... of our
baby.
Yes, of course.
You don't need to worry about that.
His name is...
Naruto.
Minato and I.
Together, we both picked that name out of
the pages.
Of Jiraiya Sensei's novel.
Naruto, you say?
Very well.
I'll take responsibility.
But now, for the sake of your child,
you must rest.
Kushina.
I'll keep my promise.
[birds chirping]
[yawns]
Huh!?
What... Huh!?
What the hell is this?
Naruto Uzumaki!
That's me!
One day, I'll be hokage!
Damn!
It's that kid again!
Thanks to him, we have another big mess to
clean up.
Yeah, and he doesn't even have any parents
that we can go and complain to about it.
What'll we do?
Who's going to pay to get all of this
cleaned up?
Who can we complain to, you know?
It was him again, wasn't it?
Yeah, the boy we're not supposed to talk
about.
That kid's a nuisance.
He's so unpleasant.
More like useless.
See you later!
Wait, your lunch!
Oops, thanks.
What did you put in there for me anyway?
I said I wanted an omelet!
Well, good, because that's what I made you
both.
You be careful!
Okay!
May I come in?
Here's this month's allowance.
Make sure you spend it wisely.
Hold on.
Tell me about them.
Tell me all about my mom and dad.
I'm certain that I told you before.
Although it was quite some time ago.
I don't mean that!
You're talking about when the nine-tailed
fox ran amok, aren't you?
I already know plenty about how it
attacked the village.
And killed tons of people, including my
parents.
But that stuff isn't what I'm asking you
to tell me about now!
What I want to know is...
Just who were my parents, really?
What kind of people were they?
There's no use in asking such questions.
It won't bring back the dead.
Look over there.
Isn't he that boy?
I think so.
That's him, isn't it?
That boy gives me the creeps.
Hey, you see him?
Don't play with that kid.
You never know what he's gonna do.
Is that guy right?
Man, that looks good!
Hey, Pops, give me an order of fried rice
and dumplings.
You got it!
An order of dumplings for me, too.
What a weird kid.
That was that boy.
Did you hear the rumors that Lord Forth
died because of him?
So that's him, huh?
I'm home.
What?
Wow!
Hey, Mom?
Seconds, please.
Sure thing.
Big Brother said that you're going on a
trip somewhere.
When do you leave?
Yes, that's right.
We're going to visit your mother's family.
Oh.
So Itachi told you all about our trip,
did he?
I thought that we could go on my next day
off.
You wanna come?
I'm gonna have Big Brother teach me all
kinds of stuff.
He said he'd teach you?
Oh, yeah.
He promised that he would.
Itachi did?
That's unusual.
Oh, here's your rice, dear.
Oh, could I trouble you for some tea?
Sure.
Hey!
Here.
Go on, Gramps.
Eat up.
Oh, thank you for sharing this.
Oh, it looks really tasty.
Yeah, well, I was the one who caught it.
So, of course, it's gonna taste really
good.
Oh, hot, hot!
Just look at all those stars.
Each one of them is a sun like the one
that shines down on our world.
What do you think?
The sheer amount is incredible,
eh?
The sun?
That giant thing that shines in the sky
during the day?
That's right.
The universe is limitless.
Yeah?
Wow, you sure know a lot of stuff,
Gramps.
Compared to the
vastness of the world, the
existence that each
person leads is insignificant.
The things that we inconsequential humans
worry about are often very petty indeed.
You're right.
So this world is as big as all that,
huh?
It seems like it just goes on and on.
Hey, Gramps, do you want some mushroom
soup?
Are you sure you can spare me some?
Sure.
You know, you tell great stories,
Gramps.
I see.
Are you sure these mushrooms are safe?
Won't know till we eat them, you know.
Yes, you're right.
Now you try.
Just like that.
You've improved, Sasuke.
I can throw better than Mom now.
All right.
How about this?
Big Brother You're amazing, Big Brother.
How'd you even get them to do that?
You'll be throwing like that soon.
You're quite a lot like me, you know that?
Big Brother, can you teach me again
sometime, like today?
Sure.
When I have the time.
You promise?
Yeah.
Do you know how the Uchiha Clan came
about?
What?
No, I haven't really learned about it too
much yet.
The Uchiha Crest is the symbol and proof
of our prestigious clan.
An image of a fan is prestigious?
You need wind to start a fire,
right?
You produce wind with a fan.
And is that something amazing?
Well, you'll come to understand in time.
Big Brother, for the sake of the clan,
is that why you fight?
I wonder.
I'm not entirely sure about that just yet
either.
All right, I'm gonna make us a big feast
tonight.
Ooh, hot!
You made all this just for the two of us?
Uh, yeah.
But maybe I went a little overboard.
Yeah, just a little.
I'm totally stuffed.
Hey Sasuke, wanna sleep outside tonight?
Are you sure it's okay for us to do that?
Hey, careful!
Don't be in such a rush!
Ow!
Are you cold?
Uh-uh.
It feels great out here.
I really want to become a
skilled shinobi like you because
that way I'll finally be able
to get Father's approval.
You wanna be like me?
No.
You'll surpass me.
That's impossible.
No way.
I mean, you're this super gifted genius.
Everyone says that, you know.
You know, you are a lot like me.
You do have the potential.
Okay then, I'll surpass you.
Sasuke.
Okay.
Hey, Sakura.
I was thinking, don't those bangs of yours
get in the way?
You should just cut them off.
Oh, don't start, dear.
Girls have their reasons to do what they
do.
If you say things like that to her,
then Sakura's going to start hating you.
Oh, you like flowers, huh?
Who?
Oh.
It's you, Ino.
You like those cosmos flowers?
Oh, uh, um, I guess so, yeah.
Hey, here, take a look at this.
Ta-da!
Oh, how pretty.
I know, right?
I could tie your hair up with this if you
want.
Huh?
You want to tie up my hair?
You're really cute, Sakura.
Don't hide it.
Now... there.
This looks way better on you, don't you
think?
But this way... it's just... my forehead
is a billboard brow.
People only tease you because you try to
cover it up.
Just flaunt it, and don't let them get to
you.
Then everybody around you will change.
But Ino, you're so strong, and I'm...
I think that this is a much better look
for you, don't you?
You've got a good sense of style.
I think that you just need to have more
confidence.
I, um, well, I think that I made a friend.
Her name is Ino Yamanaka, and she's this
totally incredible person.
She's cute, strong, fashionable,
and really kind, too.
Wow, I see.
You made a friend, Sakura?
Well, if she's cute like you say,
then I would love to meet her.
Oh, dear.
Why would you say something like that?
I'm really happy for you, Sakura.
You have to make sure that you cherish
your friends.
Always remember, in this life,
friends are your most precious assets.
Okay.
Ino even gave me this ribbon in my hair.
And it looks great on you!
You know, you're as cute as your mother
was when she was young.
Oh, dear, don't embarrass me.
Did you actually say that I'm cute?
Sakura, while you're at it, you should
find a boyfriend, too.
Dad, stop!
Wow, that's amazing!
You did this all by yourself?
It's nothing, really.
I mean, I'm not that creative.
Not like you are.
Although... Do you see this cosmos flower?
To bring out its beauty more, the things
around it should complement it.
So the elements of the arrangement don't
clash.
Hold on.
Let me try something, okay?
Like... this.
So... what do you think?
How's it look?
You know, there's this boy.
And, well, I have a really big crush on
him.
Oh, yeah?
I had no idea.
So who is this mystery boy?
And is this the whole reason why you've
been acting so much more cheerful lately?
Okay, all done!
No, not really.
Or at least I don't think so.
But Sasuke is just...
Oh, okay, I see.
So it's Sasuke, huh?
There's a rumor that Sasuke likes girls
who have long hair.
And so I've been trying
to... Sorry, you know what?
I just remembered something.
I'll come again later.
Hey, wait!
Ino!
Thank you for today!
All right.
I believe that will do for today.
No!
Please, Father.
I can still keep going with today's
training.
Meiji, don't overdo it.
But, considering your age, you've gotten
strong.
Father, thank you for that and also for
sparring with me.
Oh, Father.
There's something I've been meaning to ask
you.
I've heard my uncle, your older brother,
has a child like me.
Is that true?
Yes.
A girl.
She's one year younger than you.
A girl, huh?
We're going to her third birthday
celebration tomorrow.
I wonder what she's like.
Father, take a look.
It's starting to snow.
Wow!
The year's first.
Looks like it'll be heavy.
Lady Hinata, congratulations on your third
birthday.
Lady Hinata?
She's a really cute kid.
Meiji, there's something that you must
know.
It's your destiny to protect her and the
Hyuga bloodline.
The Hyuga bloodline?
Father!
Meiji is very strong.
You know, back when the two of us lived
only for the sake of Lady Hinata.
That's the Hyuga destiny.
Good!
That will do for today.
Meiji, you're indeed strong.
And Hinata, you still have a ways to go.
Well, my father's daily lessons are...
I don't like practicing Taijutsu.
What are you even talking about?
You're the successor of the Hyuga clan.
You're very important.
You have to be more positive and
confident.
I wish that I could switch places with
you, big brother.
You're so strong.
No, you must never say anything such as
that.
Now listen, I will make you strong.
If you're in danger, I'll give my life to
protect you.
Brother Meiji...
Lady Hinata, it's snowing!
Today, I got to have a snowball fight with
my father.
And I was even able to hit him twice!
Let's see, the symbol on the far right
belongs to us, the Akimichi clan, right?
And the other two are...
The middle one is the Nara clans, and
the leftmost one is the Yamanaka clans.
Three clans that use highly unusual secret
ninjutsu.
We've been combining our
powers for many generations
now, and the three clans
share a special relationship.
To strengthen our union
and protect our clans, the
Sarutobi clan bestows ear
piercings upon the three of us.
And every generation, the members of our
clan swear an oath of loyalty on those
earrings, so they're not just mere
decorations, son.
You mean these?
I saw that the other clan leaders also
wear them.
It must hurt to get your ears pierced.
We wear these piercings so the message
sinks in deep.
They constantly remind us of the oaths we
swore.
And you're eventually going to have to
have it done too, Choji.
What?
But why?
From the time my child becomes a Genin,
until he or she finally achieves Chunin
status, I am to follow custom and pass on
my piercings to him or her.
It's a practice that's
intended to teach one's child
all about the oaths
that one day, they'll take.
Yeah, but I really don't like pain.
He's Zashi.
Neji's only four.
Oh, it's such a pity.
Big Brother Neji...
Hey!
What are you doing?
What are you doing out here in the snow
like this?
And if you just keep crying, how am I
gonna find out?
I...
Listen, where's your house?
Oh, come on now.
Look, let's go.
Wow, look at this place.
You live in a big house like this,
and you're out here crying?
I'm alone.
I don't have anyone, but I never cry.
I mean, for real, I never, ever cry.
Bye!
Hinata!
You're the heir to the main family.
You're very important.
Just what do you think you're doing out
here?
I... For your sake, and
for the sake of the main
family, many people have
made the ultimate sacrifice.
It's time that you learned about such
things, young lady.
Here goes!
Pops away!
Bullseye!
Operation Red Nose Hokage is complete!
He's incorrigible.
Lord Hokage, please, I... I need to think
about this.
I don't know about becoming Naruto's
teacher.
As you know, nearly every single person in
this village is troubled by Naruto's
mischief, and his irksome
pranks are becoming
more and more troublesome
each and every day.
No one wants to take him on as a student.
I believe that a teacher's job is to
enhance each student's inherent virtues.
Now listen, if Naruto
isn't able to graduate
from the academy, he
cannot become a ninja.
He'll remain an outcast in this village
for the rest of his life.
Surely someone else is a better fit?
If he cannot find a
teacher, then I'll have no
other choice but to expel
Naruto from the academy.
Just forget about it.
No one's going to blame you
for how you feel, and even if we
do have to kick him out, it
certainly wouldn't be your fault.
Please, wait.
What's that?
Then you've decided to take the job?
Uh, well, fine.
Oh, excellent.
That's really good to hear.
You've no idea how much good this will do
Naruto.
And keep wiping until every speck of that
graffiti is gone!
Look, it's that... that kid.
Why do they even let that boy stay in the
village anyway?
Motoko, you should have more consideration
for us.
Shut up!
Hey, come back here!
I'm not that kid!
I'm Naruto Uzumaki!
And I'm going to be Hokage one day!
It was just a dream.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Almost forgot, I start a new class today.
Well, you never get a second chance to
make a good first impression.
I gotta give him the greeting that he
deserves.
Come on, Akamaru.
Hey, where are you going?
Come on!
Who did this?
Of all the juvenile pranks.
I got you that eraser was nothing but a
decoy!
And you totally fell for it too!
Naruto?
Yeah, I know.
Go stand in the hallway.
No, go and take your seat.
What a letdown.
I was sure you'd get yelled at.
I was kind of looking forward to it to
tell you the truth.
This place is so boring!
Good morning!
First, allow me to introduce myself.
Starting today, I'm your new homeroom
teacher, Iruka Umino.
My favorite food is Ichiraku Ramen.
And my least favorite food is mixed rice.
I was born on May 26th, so I'm a Gemini.
Therefore,
a person's chakra is greatly influenced by
that person's mental energy.
Hold on.
Sensei, isn't it already time for class to
be over?
What?
Just look.
See for yourself.
Oh, I didn't realize it was so late.
Well then, that's everything for today.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I knew he'd fall for that old trick.
That makes prank number three!
Boy, that's smart.
But how did you figure it out so quickly?
Just return to your seat.
And we'll continue.
All right, everyone.
Instead of just introducing
yourselves, I want each
of you to demonstrate
your skill with Ninjutsu.
Don't worry, you're not going to be graded
on this.
It's merely so I can assess
where you are in your
studies and plan how to
proceed with our lessons.
Okay, we'll start off with a basic clone
jutsu then.
And the first up...
is Sasuke Uchiha.
Want to give it a shot?
Using clone jutsu is even easier than
child's play.
Why do you always have to act so smug all
the time?
It's so annoying!
Just shut up, you loser.
Leave Sasuke alone.
You'll break his concentration.
Yeah, that's right.
You're just in the way, loser.
Come on.
Not you too, Sakura.
Okay, Sasuke.
Give it a try.
Huh.
Clone jutsu.
Wow.
Amazing, Sasuke.
It's a perfect clone jutsu.
I can't tell which one's real and which
one's fake.
Oh, please.
It's totally obvious to me.
This one!
Wrong, as usual.
Huh?
What?
Blockhead!
Back off!
That's the real Sasuke!
Get away from him!
Yeah!
Looks like you picked wrong again.
Oh, Sasuke.
That's amazing.
Two clones at once.
While the real Sasuke moved away unseen.
So what?
I can do clone jutsu too.
Watch this.
Clone jutsu!
That kid can't do anything right.
Listen, I don't know what your problem is,
loser.
But just stay away from me, you got that?
All you're doing is interrupting our
lesson.
You're wasting the time of everyone here
and becoming an annoyance.
What?
He's right.
But you're not just becoming an annoyance.
That's all you've ever been or will be.
Hey, that's cruel, Hibachi.
But sometimes the truth hurts.
What?
Why you?
Listen up.
Stop ganging up on Naruto.
Sensei.
Leave him alone.
Just ignore him.
Huh?
All right, everyone.
Come on.
We still have a class to finish.
Yes, Sensei.
Come on, Akamaru.
We're into some water.
All right.
Elder Sister Hinata.
I've been waiting for you.
Now come on.
Let's go and play ninja.
I'm sorry, Hanabi.
But I can't right now.
Pretty please?
Just for a little bit?
That will not do, Lady Hanabi.
Lady Hinata is scheduled to train with
Lord Hiyashi now.
But I'll play with you.
Please be on your way.
Okay.
See you later, Hanabi.
No!
Don't go!
Elder Sister!
This is boring.
Well, I'm sorry, but it can't be helped.
Lady Hinata is the successor of the main
family.
Yeah, but she could play a little.
The hyuga is a distinguished clan.
Within the leaf were the
only ones who possessed
the Byakugan, the most
touted of the Kekkei Genkai.
As the future leader of
the clan, Lady Hinata has a
veritable mountain of
knowledge that she must learn.
Now, here you go.
Lady Hanabi!
Oh dear, where in the world could she have
run off to?
I found Elder Sister!
I didn't get to play with Elder Sister at
all today.
Elder Sister Hinata!
I'm sorry that I'm late.
Not at all!
Damn!
Today I'll get him!
Damn it!
Oh man, come on!
Joji too?
Damn it!
Today is going to be the day I beat him
for sure!
Definitely!
I will beat him!
Alright, it's Naruto Uzumaki vs Sasuke
Uchiha-Come on!
Let's just do this, idiot!
Hey, stop that, Naruto!
You need to make the proper spar sign
before you two begin.
It's simple etiquette.
I don't care about any of that stuff!
I just want to hurry up and defeat this
jerk already!
It's time for a new Mr. Popular around
here, you know?
Whatever, loser.
But I'll make it quick if that's what you
want.
Enough!
Both of you!
Good grief.
Shinobi hand-to-hand
combat is a traditional
drill passed down from
generation to generation.
You might think it's
stuffy to be so formal, but
here at the academy we
have respect for tradition.
This stuff matters!
First you always face
and make this one-handed
sign toward your
opponent before starting.
It represents half of the
two hands used to activate
a jutsu and indicates
your intention to fight.
Now we call this the spar sign.
When you finish sparring and the bout is
concluded, you each extend forth the
unison sign and lock your fingers around
each other's.
This indicates that you recognize each
other as comrades.
That's the etiquette of Shinobi
hand-to-hand combat.
Are you listening, Naruto?
I've explained it twice now!
Yeah, yeah.
Come on.
One yes is fine, you fool!
I get it, okay?
Now to turn that kid into the.
..
Begin!
Whoa, he's so cool!
Oh, Sasuke.
..
Sasuke...
That look in his eyes...
It's the same look that everyone gives me.
No... No, it's
stronger than that.
Wait...
It's not for me...
Mani pisses me off!
I'll show them!
I'll show them all!
I'm just as good as they are!
Clone jutsu!
Damn it!
Okay, one more try!
What's the matter, Naruto?
Oh, it's nothing.
I see.
Want some ramen?
I can't pay.
Just pay me back when you're rich.
Besides, the stove's still on.
You really mean it?
You bet.
Yes!
You're the best!
You seem kinda down.
Something wrong?
It's nothing really.
I'm the same as always.
All right, kids.
Today, we're hands-on with Shuriken Jutsu.
First, let's have someone demonstrate it
for us.
Let's see... Um... Ooh!
Ooh!
Yo, right here!
Leave it to me!
I can do it!
Hit me!
I'll do it in one try!
I knew it!
Come on, give me a shot!
I'm right here!
Oh, come on!
What will you do?
Shino, you go ahead.
Iruka-sensei, I'm afraid you've chosen the
wrong person for this.
The Shuriken Jutsu is not so good.
This is something the Aburame Clan
practices.
For all forms of warfare, we rely almost
exclusively on parasitic insects.
We house them inside
our bodies... Okay, Shino!
That's enough!
Come on, Sasuke, please just show us the
basics.
He's so full of himself!
Since when does acting stuck-up make you
popular?
Yeah, way to
go!
Well done, Sasuke.
Excellent example.
Sasuke, you are so cool!
He's so cool!
Ha!
Suck-up and a show-off!
I could do that too if I wanted to,
you know.
All right, then I guess you're up next,
Naruto.
Sweet!
I'll show you how it's done!
Get ready to be amazed!
I gotta do it in one throw too.
That'll make everyone sit up and finally
take notice.
Let's go!
What a joke!
That's the worst attempt I've ever seen!
Yeah, I was just fooling around,
you guys!
Sensei, you just gotta let me try one more
time!
You just gotta!
I can do this!
No, that's enough.
Okay, which one of you wants to give it a
shot next?
Damn it!
Where'd that little brat run off to this
time?
Serves you right!
Huh?
Hey, did you know that everyone in the
Uchiha clan was killed?
Yeah, I heard my father talking about it a
while ago.
Sasuke's the only one who survived!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Oh, hey guys!
So, what's the story?
What are you doing this afternoon?
Nothing with you.
Get lost, Naruto!
Ah, come on!
We'll have lots of fun together!
Just let me hang out with you guys,
and you'll see!
No way!
Forget it!
Not now, and not tonight for the test of
courage, either.
The test of courage?!
Why'd you have to tell them about that?
Wow!
Sounds like fun!
Just tell me where to go, and I'll be
there!
We told you you can't come with us!
Got it!
And don't try to follow us!
Come on, guys!
Got it!
And don't try to follow us!
Is that the boy everyone talks about?
Which one?
Yeah, that's him.
Hey, you little brat!
Get out of here!
You know what?
Elder sister can't help you.
She came to visit me yesterday.
With her training, she must be tired.
I hope you thanked her properly.
I couldn't.
She fell asleep.
Okay.
But thank her next time.
Hey, what's the big idea, buddy?
I don't want you here.
You're nothing but a pest!
But I wasn't even doing anything!
I mean, I was just looking at the masks
you have.
Why, you pathetic little loser!
Here, is this what you want?
Then just take it and get lost.
And don't come back!
Natsu?
Who's that boy?
Oh, well...
It's like the shopkeeper said.
Just stop!
Alright?
Just stop looking at me like that!
Listen closely.
You must never go near that boy,
okay?
Oh, is it study time?
Uh-huh!
I can write my whole name now!
I even know some kanji!
Look!
Lots, actually!
Really?
Lady Hinata, don't keep Lord Hiyashi
waiting.
Right.
See you later, Hanabi!
Okay!
She's training, huh?
Focus, please.
You can't go out to play until you've
finished your work.
So strong, yet so kind.
I want to be just like her.
I want to be more like Elder Sister,
even if it's just a little bit.
Ah!
Elder Brother Neji?
Why do I have to be her sparring partner?
Please just let me train on my own.
No.
Not yet.
Continue.
Let's keep going!
Please, Neji!
Very well, then.
He's acting different today.
What's wrong, Lady Hinata?
This isn't child's play now.
Hang in there, Elder Sister.
So... That was nothing!
And you expect to fulfill your destiny?
As leader of the Hyuga?
Ah!
What is it?
My head!
The brazen fool!
What is going on?
What
is she doing out here?
Okay!
Clone Jutsu!
Wasn't he the one?
Why is Elder Sister here with him?
Elder Sister?
Ah!
I'm coming in.
Sheesh!
Some test of courage, you cowards!
None of you wimps is brave enough to go
all the way in?
You don't have to call us names,
you know.
Whatever.
Move it, loser.
This isn't so bad, I guess.
All I have to do is take one of those
sticks.
Ah!
It's a monster box!
What in the world is going on?
We saw a monster box!
What?
Serves them right!
Those chickens all got scared and ran off!
Ha!
You better run, Sensei, or the fox will
get you too!
Did you hear the news?
The advance troops were defeated.
No.
They're all dead then?
What?
The advance troops are... are all dead?
It's not true.
It can't be true.
My mom and dad can't be dead.
They can't.
It isn't true!
Hm?
What's the matter, Sensei?
Look, Naruto.
Don't you realize what you're doing by
pulling these pranks all the time?
There it is again!
I don't understand it!
Everybody!
Even you!
My own teacher!
Why does everybody look at me like that
all the time?
I'm not just a nuisance or some kind of
germ I'm a person too!
I am!
I'm Naruto Uzumaki!
Don't forget it!
No, wait!
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning, Sensei!
All right, first let me take attendance.
Naruto's not here?
Who cares?
He's such a loser.
Sakura!
You know where he is?
No.
I didn't notice he was gone.
Yeah, I don't think I even saw him this
morning.
Kiba, did you see him?
No, I didn't see him.
And I have no interest in seeing him.
Right, Akamaru?
All right, then.
Let's just start class.
But why not?
Lord Hokage is busy with his official
duties.
I don't understand.
Did he give a reason why he won't see me?
That's not our concern.
We have our orders.
No one is permitted to enter.
Hello there.
Huh?
You know, this is my favorite spot.
But I can't really
concentrate on my reading
with all that sighing
going on down there.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'll just go.
No, don't bother.
I was just about to leave.
See ya.
What's wrong?
You look depressed.
If you feel like talking, I'll listen.
Kakashi.
That's your name, right?
The thing is, I happen to be...
I'm Naruto Uzumaki's homeroom teacher.
Really?
I went to ask the third Hokage to relieve
me from my assignment.
But he wouldn't see me.
Truth is, I don't have any idea how to
deal with that boy.
Nothing works.
I don't know why the Hokage thought I was
the right person for this.
I'm just not qualified to teach a kid like
Naruto.
Perhaps you've forgotten a basic rule of
teaching.
You cannot open the mind of another unless
you have an open mind yourself.
Or perhaps there's something else you're
trying to forget.
The nine tail sealed inside of Naruto is
responsible for my parents' deaths.
I'm fully aware that Naruto is not to
blame for what occurred back then.
But whenever I look
at him, I can't stop
thinking about what's
hiding deep inside of him.
And about what the nine tails did.
I don't think someone like me can make
Naruto open up.
Actually, you are the only one who can
reach Naruto's heart.
And that... That is
your personal ordeal.
My ordeal?
Yes, Lord Hokage has presented you with a
personal ordeal.
I believe if you can
just hang in there a little
longer, you will find
the way to reach Naruto.
Rise up to meet the Hokage's expectations.
So long.
The third Hokage sure made a bold
decision.
Time to go!
Taichi!
Dinner time!
Let's go home, everyone!
Mom!
What do you think you're doing?
I told you not to play with that boy.
Come on, let's go.
Shikamaru!
Come on, let's go!
All right, Dad.
You too, Choji.
We said we'd walk you home.
Now let's go, you two.
Let's move!
See you, Naruto!
Later.
Yeah.
Bye.
Dad, let go of my hand.
What?
Are you embarrassed to be seen with your
old man?
Thank you.
Thank you for the food.
No, let me
go!
Who's that at my door?
And why are they here so early?
What?
Iruka Sensei?
Why is he coming to see me here?
Hey, Naruto!
Naruto!
You here?
Is this all he ever eats?
Thanks for the food.
You're going to Choji's later,
aren't you?
Better hurry.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Dad, can I ask you about something
that's been bugging me?
What is it?
It's about Naruto.
Why does everybody avoid him like the
plague?
Did he do something wrong?
Shikamaru, why don't you tell me how you
feel about Naruto?
You want to know how I feel?
Huh, I never thought about it before.
Well, he's not the sharpest knife in the
drawer, but he's pretty funny.
I don't think we'll
ever be buddies or
anything, but it's not
like I want to avoid him.
Well, then, ignore the others.
I say treat him however you want to.
Yeah, that's exactly what I'll do.
Ha!
I knew I'd find you here.
Hey, Shigamaru, can you lend me some
money?
Wait, let me guess why.
For some snacks again?
Yeah!
I mean, what else is there to buy besides
snacks?
And even if there was, why would you want
it?
Oh man, what a drag.
You know, you're one in a million.
What's with your eyes?
They're so creepy!
Yeah, don't even look at us, you weirdo!
Come on, cut it out!
Leave her alone!
What'd she do to you anyway?
What, you want to be a big hero or
something?
You shouldn't pick on people weaker than
you, you know?
What?
Just shut up, kid!
Whatever, this is boring.
Let's go, guys.
Yeah, this is boring.
Let's go!
Man, what a drag.
I can't believe him doing stuff like that.
Instead of butting into other people's
business, he should be polishing his skills.
Stupid Naruto.
Don't call him that.
Huh?
What?
Naruto isn't stupid.
I mean, even you said that in shogi all the
pieces are necessary, and you said that.
..
about me.
Huh?
What are you talking about, Choji?
You're just mad at me because I didn't
loan you any money before, that's all.
You're wrong.
Naruto is...
Naruto's like you, Shikamaru.
Don't call him stupid.
Now take it back.
Man, what a drag.
Listen, at least try and make sense when
you talk.
Don't... Don't you
order me around.
Hey!
What are you guys doing?
Come on, stop it!
You guys are friends, aren't you?
Why are you fighting?
Hey!
Stop!
Cause... this fatso started complaining.
Shikamaru, open your eyes!
I'm not a fatso!
I'm pleasantly plump.
All right.
Let me buy into this fight.
Huh?
What's that mean?
Oh, then I'm gonna buy snacks with all the
money you'll pay me.
What?
What's that about?
Yeah,
that's exactly what I did.
And then I went to the usual spot.
You guys know the place, right?
So that's what happened.
Naruto, you want some chips?
Oh, yeah, thanks.
Hey, look!
What?
Seriously?
What a drag.
Man, forget that.
No girls for me.
Look out, she's coming!
Look out!
Oh, man.
That Ina, she's terrified when she's mad.
What a drag.
I swear she's gonna end up in a hole of
pain.
See you later, Naruto.
Your sexy jutsu was awesome.
Bye-bye, Naruto.
Hey, Shigemaru, it's curry night at my
house tonight.
That sounds great.
I'm getting tired of my mom's cooking.
Kay, see ya!
See you tomorrow!
Come here!
Naruto, come back here!
You're gonna get my hands on you?
You crossed the line this time,
Naruto!
Give it up!
You're just bent because you don't have
the guts to do what I do.
Do ya, losers, wannabes?
You'll never catch me!
Lord Hokage, it's an emergency!
I hope you're not bothering me with some
trivia.
And don't tell me it's Naruto again.
It is Naruto again!
He climbed onto the great stone faces!
He put graffiti all over the Hokage!
Naruto!
Hold on!
That was too easy!
Oh yeah, Naruto!
Where'd you come from, Iruka-sensei?
What are you doing here?
No, what are you doing here?
You're supposed to be in class.
We will now start the final exam.
When your name is called, proceed to the
testing room.
The final test will be
on... The clone jutsu.
That's my worst technique!
Great!
I'm never gonna pass!
Alright, get it together, Naruto!
You can do this!
Believe it!
Clone jutsu!
You failed!
Iruka-sensei.
He's off, but his moves weren't bad,
and he did hang in there and replicate.
This is his third try, so you know he
really wants to become a ninja.
We could cut him a break and pass him.
Mizuki-sensei.
The other students created at least three
effective replications.
But Naruto could only create one.
And look at it.
It's pitiful.
I can't pass him.
See that?
They called me first!
I'm proud of you, son.
We all are.
There.
You see him?
It's that boy.
I heard he's the only one who failed.
Well, it serves him right.
Just imagine what would happen if he
became a ninja.
I mean, he's the boy who... Shh!
We're not allowed to talk about that.
Iruka.
There's something we need to talk about.
Iruka-sensei's tough, but he's not against
you.
Then why?
Why only me?
He wants you to be strong with all his
heart.
But that will never happen if he goes easy
on you.
He's like you, you know.
No parents, no family.
But... this time I really wanted to
graduate.
Then I guess I have to tell you.
Huh?
It's a secret, but I'm gonna let you in on
it.
A secret?
Iruka.
What is it, Lord Hokage?
I know how you feel.
You grew up just like Naruto.
Without knowing the love of a mother and
father.
The warmth of a family.
It's getting closer!
Don't let it near the village!
Let me go!
My mom and dad are still fighting back
there!
Iruka-sensei, wake up!
What?
What is it?
You need to come to Lord Hokage's right
away.
It's Naruto.
He stole the sacred scroll.
You mean the scroll of ceiling?
No!
Let's see.
The first one is...
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Not this again!
It's my worst Jutsu!
Lord Hokage, this is not just a prank!
This is a serious crime!
That scroll contained secrets that were
sealed by the first Hokage.
Secrets known only to our village!
If it falls into the wrong hands,
they can destroy our entire way of life.
All right.
Bring Naruto here at once, sir!
Where would he go?
Now that I told everyone what Naruto did,
I can eliminate him.
I'm glad he's gone.
And of course, I keep the scroll for
myself.
It's all over.
Huh?
Got me already.
Not bad.
You're quick, Sensei.
I only had time to learn one technique.
He's been out here practicing.
I can tell how hard he's been working.
Listen, Aruka Sensei.
I'm going to show you this amazing Jutsu
and you're going to let me graduate.
Then everything will be okay.
That's the way it works, right?
Anyone who learns a Jutsu from this scroll
passes.
Huh?
Where'd you get that idea?
Mizuki Sensei told me about it.
Believe it!
He told me where to find the scroll and
this place.
Huh?
Mizuki?
Look out!
I see you found our little hideaway.
So that's the way it is, huh?
I should have known.
Naruto!
Give me the scroll now!
Wait a minute!
What's going on here?
Naruto!
Don't let Mizuki get the scroll!
He contains forbidden Jutsu that could put
this village in grave danger.
Mizuki used you to get the scroll for
himself, for his own power!
Naruto...
Iruka's just trying to scare you because
he doesn't want you to have the scroll.
Stop lying, Mizuki!
Don't let him trick you, Naruto!
Oh, I'll tell you who's really lying.
No, Mizuki!
They've been lying to you your whole life,
Naruto.
Since the decree twelve years ago.
What decree?
Everyone knows except you.
Iruka's trying to hide it from you even
now.
He'd do anything to shut me up.
What is this decree?
Why does everyone else know about it?
Don't tell him!
It's forbidden!
The decree is no one can tell you the
nine-tailed fox is inside you.
The fox spirit that
killed Iruka's parents and
destroyed our village
has taken over your body.
You are the nine-tailed fox.
Stop it!
They've all been sneaking around,
hiding things from you your whole life.
Didn't you think it was strange how they
treated you?
Like dirt.
Like they hated you for just being alive.
No!
No, no, no, no!
Naruto... That's why you will
never be accepted in this village.
Even your beloved Sensei hates your guts.
Die, Naruto!
Naruto, get down!
Why?
Because we're the same.
When I lost my parents, no one seemed to
care.
They didn't have time for me.
They just forgot I was there.
My grades dropped.
I became the class clown.
I just wanted them to see me and to know
my name.
My schoolwork wasn't good enough to get
their attention.
So I did crazy things.
And then I had to pay for it.
It was hard.
I know that's how you feel, Naruto.
You feel lonely and it hurts inside.
And I could have been there for you more.
But I let you down.
I'm sorry.
No one should have to suffer that much.
No one should be alone like that.
Naruto!
You know, once he makes up his mind,
nothing can change it.
He's going to use the scroll to take
revenge on the village.
You saw that look in his eye, didn't you?
Those are the eyes of a beast.
No.
Naruto isn't like that.
You're a joke.
I'm going to get Naruto and get the
scroll.
I'll be back for you.
Naruto!
Everything Mizuki said was a lie!
Give me the scroll!
Hurry!
He's coming after you to take it away!
It can't be.
How did you know, Naruto?
How did you know that it was me and not
Iruka?
Because I... Iruka.
You're a fool.
Why are you protecting that freak?
He's the one that wiped out your family.
I don't care what you say.
You're not getting your hands on that
scroll.
As if you could stop me.
Don't you get it?
Naruto is just like me.
How's that?
He wants the scroll for his own power and
his own vengeance.
That's how beasts are.
He'll pour all his rage into the scroll
and destroy everything.
You're right.
So it's true.
Iruka-sensei never believed in me.
He thinks I'm some beast.
Some kind of freak!
That is how beasts are.
But that's not who Naruto is.
He's nothing like that.
Naruto's one of a kind.
Works hard, puts his whole heart into it.
Sure, he messes up sometimes and everyone
jumps on him.
But his suffering only makes him stronger.
That's what separates him from being a
beast.
So you're wrong.
He's nothing like the nine-tailed fox.
He's Naruto Uzumaki.
Of the village hidden in the leaves.
You really believe that drivel?
Iruka, I was going to save you for later,
but I changed my mind.
You're finished!
Naruto!
Not bad for a little punk.
If you ever lay a hand on my sensei...
I'll kill you!
Such big words.
I can completely destroy you with a single
move!
Take your best shot, fool!
I'll give it back to you a thousand-fold!
Let's see you try!
Show me what you can do, nine-tailed fox!
Shadow clone jutsu!
Namuto...
Those aren't just illusions.
They're solid clones.
He's mastered an extremely advanced jutsu.
What is this?
If you're not coming, then we're going to
come after you.
Sorry, I kind of got carried away.
You okay, Iruka-sensei?
Yeah...
Naruto, come here a minute.
I've got something I want to give you.
You're telling me no one can find Naruto?
Not a clue.
This is bad news.
We've got to smoke him out or something.
There's no longer any need to worry.
Lord Hokage!
The scroll's safe.
Naruto will be back soon.
Sensei, how much longer?
Okay, you can open your eyes now.
Congratulations.
You graduate.
And to celebrate, I have a surprise.
We're going out for ramen tonight.
Iruka-sensei!
That hurts!
Naruto, this is only the beginning.
The road gets tougher now that you're a
ninja.
But if I told you that, I guess it would
ruin the moment.
So I'll tell you later.
Over ramen.
It was coincidence.
But even so, it appears that Naruto has
saved the entire village.
You may leave now.
Yes, sir.
What is it?
Lord Hokage, I just...
I just wanted to thank you for placing me
in charge of Naruto, sir.
It's because of that assignment.
I remembered why I wanted to do this.
Why I wanted to be a teacher.
It all started with something you told me,
Lord Hokage.
A long, long time ago.
It's hard to believe it's been a year
already.
You're very brave.
It's hard to do that, to hide sadness
behind laughter.
Your instructors have been telling me that
you're among the most playful of all their
students and that you're always so full of
fun.
You're wrong!
I'm not sad about anything!
It's a noble thing to die in the line of
duty, isn't it?
My parents both gave their lives to
protect this place from the fox demon.
They're heroes!
I'm the son of those revered heroes.
I'm not even sad because they went and
left me all alone.
If I cry it's because I'm proud.
It's alright, Hiruka.
I know that somewhere inside of you
there's a boy curled up in a ball of pain.
But remember this.
You are not alone.
Inside every ninja of the hidden leaf
there burns the will of fire.
The will of fire?
It's what gives us the strength to defend
our village.
It's the unbreakable bond that ties us all
together.
It's what makes us a family.
I wonder, do you have it yet, young as you
are?
I think so.
I wish to pass on the will of fire to the
children of the future.
To children like Naruto.
I'm in the mountain, never coming down.
Breaking through the contents,
never falling down.
My head's still shaking, like I was
trying.
Sneaking at the classroom, by the back
door.
A morrow let me try some, but I didn't
care.
Waiting is wasted for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry cause you're so right.
Don't try to expect the worst.
Cause you were in this area in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry cause you're so right.
Don't try to expect the worst.
Cause you were hating yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry cause you're so right.